That's what I'm talking about.
That's what I'm talking about,
because I have a lot of other times, especially
in the early 14th or late,
or two, they've never in 19.
I'm going to try and log.
I'm going to leave the implication about the record
of the North Campus Ministry's Steve Quetzal.
We're going to be creating the NEO
and the athletes of the Greenlands of the South
and the athletes on the campus,
15th of the year, around the world.
We have a lot of studies in the week
to have at least the eight different groups in the week.
I have a sort of team class tonight.
So 26 guys, you can do it at a whole little world.
And visiting with a bunch of said, you know,
if you came here from your country,
you don't have to know where my whole whole world is not going
to anything about us.
People in the United States, they're poor,
poor, poor, poor, poor, poor, poor who may thrive.
And if you came to a little India, in my whole home,
they all hold shut, but I can tell you this, they do love it.
You know, the love of the people who went through the quarantine,
all the things, the last fall,
the last fall, the last quarter of the planning, the spring,
the last fall of the week, the year, the end of the week,
the rest of the teams, the travel, the rest of the Saturday,
the fall of the first two, we appreciate your support.
Plus for it.
But thank you for this time and we can get our community
further aware of their requirements,
maybe you could ask them that there's a leadership
of this community of all of this, the lessons with your all spirit.
Do you think the English, the developing,
economic planning, for our first university,
do you think they need to say that other the lessons that they apply?
Which is a pretty good way to do this.
Do you think so?
I mean, I just say something about that.
And to do the revitalization of the United States,
One nation and another, in this world, we are going to repeat the next tomorrow.
The fourth, we are going to listen to this incident agenda staff.
We are going to be able to move out of six or three, eight.
Six.
Eight.
Who is the highest partner?
Five.
The nine, also in the Associates of Master Service Agreement,
for the world of 2020 National Day.
So, the start of last festival year, we've budgeted journaling services, but we knew leadership was changing, there was a bunch of stuff happening, so normally that contract runs, July 1 to June 3 to fall in the year.
We decided to go ahead and just do six months, you know, that would change to come in and we can, if you would change to come in and be being, make sure you want to keep all of us around that city.
Here we are, six months later, it is budgeted, so we're just here to see if we want to reuse that contract through the end of the year.
Well, yes, sir.
How do we do?
If they've done a great job, of course, if possible, you have any more projects, and we want to have them to know who you have been and who you have been.
Like her.
How's that?
New year's time.
Davis?
Hi.
Thank you.
I'm staying right here.
Yeah, I'm doing it.
They don't make sure.
All right.
I don't know if you've been on Main Street last week, but the Northbound is open.
So, you can guide North up Main Street all the way and get the railroad tracks and keep going on.
You can't not go south of it.
That's still going to close.
It's going to stay closed until the asphalt line goes back up, which is, I have pulled more and more April.
But we always need to do snow and march, so that's slow to plan something in that gap.
As soon as the asphalt line opens back up, the weather starts to warm.
They're coming back on the AMA.
They will finish painting and then stripe it.
That's it.
So, the drain that's put in is working.
It's working, boss.
Actually, I think I was pulled last two days.
It was dry.
It's been dry since then.
So, it gives a job.
So, fill that track, ground water on the road.
Things look like they're starting to panic up.
So, that was a great fall.
So, all the way down now, it's for the asphalt line.
So, the asphalt line is open back up.
And striping, traffic signal at the third.
I was pulled is going to be here next month.
So, we're kind of hoping you'll probably see a change that we're coming in for time.
This job is supposed to be done in the first week in July.
So, they are wanting to give an extension to June 1.
But they don't think it's going to take you to the left.
They're talking maybe a week.
to pain and stride.
That signal, that's going to take a month or two.
But it would be coming in and figuring out the perfect,
because hopefully all of that ends about the same amount.
So, traffic signal at third, they have three line cabinets
to put in, which is why the street lights go and work.
We've found that's been, that's been a year
trying to get those cabinets away.
There's somewhere, we don't know where,
but they'll show up on these days,
and then we'll get those cabinets installed
so we can train the street lights back home.
Every excuse in the book about shipping the lights.
Taking the strike to take it,
so we are on home stretch,
but it's going to be the rest of the spring,
and in the early summer before we get the weather,
and finish it up.
The way I don't rely goes the whole way,
but yes, there is no track thing.
The surface is only on second and third,
and that's it.
So, we have the grinding marks you see in the first block
between first and second,
that's the base force and a load.
It still has one more layer going in.
That last two inches is a higher aggregate,
that's as far snowman and so it's smoother.
But yeah, it still has to build the entire street,
and main and all at first.
We're going to get the social media thumbs up.
We'll just update you to talk about the plan.
We'll probably be going to the target last.
Absolutely.
Any other questions?
Okay.
Thank you.
We're going to have the business and plan to visit
this closing of the agenda.
Well, staff reports.
They're keen to trust the community in the mountains.
We're keen to adjourn them.
Thank you.